欢迎回来
Welcome back.
你记得我吗
Do you remember me?
我是卡森医生
I'm Dr. Carson.
你在山顶寨
You're at Hilltop Colony.
你睡了一阵子了
You've been asleep for a while.
你的胎盘早期剥离了
You suffered from the condition abruptio placentae.
意思是胎盘与子宫分离
It's a separation of the placenta from uterus.
这么早出现很不寻常
It's unusual this early,
但是  可能由创伤引起
but, uh...could be caused by trauma.
-也许是因为你腹部的瘀伤  -我是不是
- Possibly the bruises on your abdomen -- - Did I-I...
流产了
...lose...?
没有
No.
只有小部分分离
Separation was small.
孩子的心率正常
Baby's heart rate is normal.
听听吧
Here, listen.
这就是
There it is.
你得缓几天
Now, you need to take it easy for a few days.
你可不想加剧分离
You don't want to exacerbate the separation any more.
我觉得你怀孕期间
And I really think you need to stay here
都该待在这里
for the duration of your pregnancy.
如果发生了别的事  我能处理
If anything else happens, I can take care of it.
你有问题吗
You have any questions?
慢点
Whoa, whoa. Easy.
慢点  慢点
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
你能再说一次吗
Can you say that again?
什么
What?
你刚说的一切
Everything you just said.
你没事吧
You, uh -- you okay?
他在哪
Where is he?
他们俩在哪
Where are they both?
这在格伦的口袋里
It was in Glenn's pocket.
亚伯拉罕只有一根雪茄
All Abraham had was a cigar.
感觉一切都不对
It feels like everything is wrong.
并非一切
Not everything.
他告诉我你会没事的
He told me that you're gonna be all right.
他说你只用在接下来几天里
He said you'll just have to take it easy
保重身体
for the next few days.
他跟我说我们得留下
He told me that we have to stay.
我们
That we, um...
他说他在附近会好些
He says it's better if he's close,
以防万一  直到孩子出生
just in case, till the baby's born.
那我们就留下
Then we'll stay.
我还在考虑
I'm still thinking about it.
你要留下
You're staying.
我也是
And so am I.
看见你起来了真好
It's nice to see you up.
花
Flowers.
是你放的
It was you.
还有你床边的
Ones on your bed, too.
我在书上看到  蓝色的花
I read somewhere that blue flowers
能激发力量  带来平静
inspire strength and calming.
绿色的呢
What's green?
放手
Release.
谢天谢地你终于醒了
Thank God you're finally awake.
你的人说你们把他们全消灭了
You people said you got them all.
我们以为如此
We thought we did.
那只是一个哨站
It was just an outpost.
他们有多少人
H-How many of them were there?
很多人
There were a lot.
也许几百个
Maybe hundreds.
他们知道你们逼我们接受的协议吗  玛莎
Do they know the deal you made us take, Marsha?
- 是玛姬  - 不知道
- It's Maggie. - No.
我们也没逼你们接受协议  格雷戈里
And we didn't make you take the deal, Gregory.
我很高兴我们能为你治疗
I...I...I'm happy we could patch you up.
你们得走了
You need to go.
确保瑞奇知道我们为你做的事
Make sure you let Rich know what we did for you.
卡森医生说我该留下
Dr. Carson said I should stay.
如果他觉得他有权做出那个决定
If he thinks he has the authority to make that decision,
那他就搞错了
he's mistaken.
别这样看着我
Don't look at me like that.
她跟自己人在一起会更安全
She'll be safer with her own people.
而我们没有她会更安全
And we'll be safer without her.
你应该和玛姬保持距离
You need to keep your distance from Maggie
专心于你在山顶寨的工作就好
and stay focused on your work here at Hilltop.
这是你干的吗
Did you do this?
我们不埋死者  而是火化
We don't bury our dead. We burn them.
这是我干的  我不住在这里
I did it. I don't live here.
格雷戈里  这位是萨沙
Gregory, this is Sasha.
是她把玛姬送来的
She got Maggie here.
她俩都是从亚历山大来的
They're both from Alexandria.
我没法...
I can't ---
我没时间记住每个人
I-I don't have time to keep track of everybody.
我也一直在修养  耶稣
I've been recuperating, too, Jesus --
养我的刀伤
from a stab wound.
明白吗
You know?
玛姬说她的人能搞定救世军
Maggie said that her people could take care of the Saviors.
但如今他们只是让我们的社区陷入险境
S-So far, all they've done is put our community at risk.
假如他们看见你在这里
You know, if they see you here,
他们会以为我们是一伙儿的
they'll think we colluded.
我们确实是一伙儿的
We did.
我可没同意你们这样做
I did not agree to this.
假如他们觉得我们帮你们袭击了哨站
If they think we helped attack their outpost,
他们也会这样对我们
they'll do that to us.
耶稣  你知不知道什么叫装糊涂
Jesus, do you have any idea what plausible deniability means?
知道
Yes.
那你就该明白  这是我们逃避惩罚的办法
Well, then you know it's our way out.
假如她俩离开  我们就能装糊涂了
If they leave, we have plausible deniability.
格雷戈里  天快黑了
Gregory, it -- it'll be night soon.
她们现在离开不安全
It's not safe for them to leave now.
你瞧  我是个好人
Look, I'm a good guy.
你们可以留下来过夜
You can stay the night.
但明早就得离开
But leave in the morning.
我们今晚再好好谈谈
We'll talk more about it tonight.
不  我心意已决
No, I made my decision.
我只是觉得  也许...
I'm just saying that maybe --
你想和她俩一起走吗
Do you want to go back with them?
我会送她俩回去的
I'll take them back.
-我的意思是...  -我知道你什么意思
- I meant -- - I know what you meant.
那就这么定了
So it's settled.
不  不行
No, it's not.
玛姬怀孕了
Maggie is pregnant.
那是她自己犯的错
Well... that's her mistake.
等等
Wait.
《行尸走肉》
你应该和我们一起去的
You should come with us.
得有人留下来照看朱迪思
Someone's got to be here for Judith.
有人可以照看的
There's people who want to help.
我们最多只出去几天而已
We'll only be gone a few days at the most.
我们需要补给
We need supplies.
他们很快就会回来了
They're gonna be coming back soon.
以后就成这样了吗
Is this how it's gonna be now?
是的
Yes.
就是这样了
It is.
你清楚的
You know that.
几天后见
See you in a few days.
我们该出发了
We should get going.
他会想明白的
He'll come around.
我...到楼下等你
I'll, uh, meet you downstairs.
你们改变主意了的话...
You change your mind...
我们往北走
we're headed north.
祝你好运
Good luck.
嗯
Yeah.
过两天见
I'll see you soon.
谢谢
Thank you.
你为什么没和我爸一起走
Why didn't you go with my dad?
我得想清楚一些事
I have to figure some things out.
有什么要想清楚的
What is there to figure out?
我们要如何做
How we can do this.
假如我们能做的话
If we can.
我们不能
We can't.
至少不是像这样
No, not like this.
你爸可不是这么想的
Your dad thinks differently.
他错了
And he's wrong.
你知道的
You know it.
虽然我确实这样想
Even if I think he is...
我不确定
...I don't know.
待会儿换绷带  对奥利维亚好点
Change your bandage later, and be nice to Olivia.
伊妮德
Enid.
我得去见玛姬
I need to see Maggie.
你要走着去山顶寨
You're walking to the Hilltop?
太远了
It's far.
没事的
I'll be fine.
也许吧
Maybe.
肯定没事
I'll be fine.
我比你射得准
I have better aim than you.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean it that way.
我不会再救你了
I'm not saving you anymore.
你是说在武器库的时候吗
That's what happened in the armory?
你觉得你救了我
You saved me?
是的
Yeah.
你安全回来了
You made it back in one piece.
你还在这
You're still here.
我说的不是那个
I'm not talking about that.
很遗憾你看到了那场面
I'm sorry you had to see it.
我不遗憾
I'm not.
我真的没法说服你
You sure I can't talk you into
去住巴林顿公馆的空房吗
taking the extra room at Barrington House?
还是要说一下  有你在我很高兴
For what it's worth, I'm glad you're here.
那就劝格雷戈里改变主意吧
Then make Gregory change his mind.
我会试试的
I'm going to try.
那还不够
It's not good enough.
当然不够
It's not.
但这里的人需要我
But the people need me here.
如果只剩下格雷戈里  可能会更糟
If it was just Gregory, it'd be worse.
那你为什么不掌权
So why aren't you in charge?
我不是那种人  我不是领袖
It's not me. I'm not a leader.
如果我走呢
What if I leave?
如果让玛姬留下
If Maggie can stay,
我会帮山顶寨搜集物资
I'll scavenge, for the Hilltop.
如果你们保护她  我会替她做贡献
I'll pay her way if you just keep her safe.
格雷戈里会同意吗
Would Gregory go for that?
也许
Maybe.
但我不想这样
But I-I don't want that.
你到底想怎样  耶稣
What do you want, Jesus?
你想要这里变成什么样
What do you want this place to be?
我...
I-I just...
我只想帮忙
I just try to help.
也许你该做得更多
Maybe you got to do more.
这个  是亚伯拉罕的
This, uh...This was Abraham's.
我在这找到的
I found it here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我很喜欢他
I liked him.
他是我认识的人中唯一一个
He was...one of the only people I'd ever met
能讲出好笑又气人的话的人
who could say things that make you smile and wince at the same time.
进
Come in.
我给你铺好床了  还摆了几件衣服
I made the bed for you and laid out some clothes.
都是我的衣服
They're mine,
所以它们更多是实用而不是舒适
so they're more utility than comfort.
没事
It's okay.
我们不会住很久
We won't be here much longer.
对所有这些事  我很抱歉
I'm sorry, about all of it.
我会试试看我能做什么
I'm...gonna see what I can do.
你们为什么火化死者
Why do you burn your dead?
是为了继续前行
The idea was just to keep going.
你们靠什么来铭记逝者呢
What do you have to remember 'em by?
靠我们自己
Us.
明早见
I'll see you in the morning.
现在怎么办
Now what?
也许我们可以硬留下
Maybe we stay.
格雷戈里能怎么样
What can Gregory do?
这里他掌权
He's in charge.
他是个傻瓜
He's an idiot.
他是懦夫
He's a coward.
懦夫更危险
They're more dangerous.
我们有一晚上时间来考虑
We have the night. Let's think on it.
早上就会想清楚了
Things will be clearer in the mornin'.
(空气)
你来这做什么
What are you doing here?
想兜兜风
Felt like a drive.
那是什么
What is that?
大门开了
The gates are open.
有火
There's fires.
音乐是从一辆车里传出来的
The music is coming from a car.
我得关了它
I have to turn that thing off.
卡森医生不让你站起来
Dr. Carson told you to stay off your feet.
我不能让你一个人去
I can't let you do this by yourself.
坐下
Sit.
去吧
Go.
耶稣
Jesus!
萨沙一个人在下面  她需要帮助
Sasha's alone down there! She needs help!
该死  玛姬
Damn it, Maggie.
你们两个
You two!
去把门关上
Get those gates closed!
好的
On it!
可恶  快点
Oh, man, come on.
-你好  -抱歉
- Hi. - ‭Sorry.
没事
It's okay.
我们得把门关上
We need to close the gates.
是的
Yeah.
萨沙
Sasha.
她可以的
She's got it.
我这需要你
I need your help here.
看到那场面你不遗憾吗
Not sorry you saw it?
遗憾
Yeah.
我眼睁睁得看着
I watched it.
两次都是
Both times.
没有移开视线
I didn't look away.
为什么
Why?
因为在那个时候
Because, when it was happening,
我知道我得牢牢记住
I knew that I needed to remember it.
所以当我有机会杀他时
So when I had the chance to kill him,
我不会犹豫
I wouldn't have a choice.
我觉得我也会杀他的
I think I'd kill him, too.
这很糟糕  但是...
It's messed up, but...
事实就是这样
that's how it is.
你会为爱的人做一些事
You do things for the ones you love.
还有爱过的人
Loved.
不是为他们
It's not for them.
我很抱歉把你锁在武器库
I'm sorry I locked you in the armory.
我不需要看那场面
I didn't need to see it.
我们甚至不知道她是否还好
We don't even know if she's okay.
我们会知道的
We'll get there.
是的
Yeah.
我不关心她们做了什么  回答是不行
I don't care what they did. The answer is no.
我不会赶走一个曾经帮过我们的孕妇
I'm not turning away a pregnant woman who helped us.
我也不会赶走萨沙
I'm not turning away Sasha, either.
-谁是萨沙  -她们要留下
- Who the hell is Sasha? - They're staying.
掌权的不是你  耶稣  是我
You're not in charge, Jesus. I am.
我才是要保证这地方安全的人
I'm the one who has to look after the safety of this place.
怎么  你是说你想管事吗
What, are you telling you want to call the plays,
经过这么长时间
after all this time,
在我打理好一切以后吗
after I set the table here?
你只要一句话
Say the word.
被破坏的门  救世军  居民
The broken gate, the Saviors, the people --
所有都是你的
all of this can be yours.
只是你得多留五分钟了
Only you'd have to stick around for more than five minutes.
你得成为这地方的一分子
You'd actually have to be a part of this place.
格雷戈里
Gregory?
我刚让凯特琳小姐
Ah, I-I was just telling Ms. Caitlin
拿一点她最出名的大黄果酱给你们
to bring up some of her famous rhubarb preserves for you both.
这是为了感谢
It's our way of saying thank you
你们昨晚的帮助
for helping out last night.
是梅特琳小姐
It's Ms. Maitlin.
当你们离开的时候可以带走
You can take them with you when you go.
你现在就该走了
And you should go now,
因为救世军随时都会回来
because the Saviors could get back any minute.
-我会走的  -萨沙
- I'll go. - Sasha...
但让她留下来
But let her stay.
-昨晚我们就算扯平了  -不成
- We'll call it even on last night. - No deal.
但是谢谢有你们在的日子
But it's been lovely having you here.
告诉我我们该怎么办
Just tell me how we can make this work.
我觉得我们俩需要...
I think we'd need to...
-单独聊聊  好好探讨...  -去死吧
- meet on that one-on-one just to explore -- - Go to hell.
你真的在暗示...
Are you actually imply--
不  不好意思
No. You know what? I'm sorry.
我得让凯特琳小姐先别端果酱上来了
I'm gonna tell Ms. Caitlin to keep her preserves.
你知道他们要发现你们在这里会做什么吗
You know what they'll do if they find you here?
耶稣  把她们藏进壁橱里
Jesus, get them in the closet.
- 格雷戈里  - 赶紧进去
- Gregory. - Go get in there now.
不许动  不许说话
And you don't move, you don't speak,
也许你们还能保住性命
and maybe you'll get out of this alive.
伊妮德
Enid.
别走了
Stop.
-你们好  -你好
- Hello. - Hello.
你是格雷戈里
You're Gregory.
正是在下
Guilty as charged.
-欢迎来到山顶寨  -谢谢
- Welcome to Hilltop Colony. - Thank you.
就当...在自己家一样吧
Do, uh... make yourself at home.
这可不是什么社交拜访
This isn't a social call.
我...我也觉得不是
I-I-I -- I wouldn't think it is.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
这地方人多闷得慌
And it's getting a little claustrophobic in here, right?
去你的书房谈吧
Let's talk in your study.
我想看看那幅画
I wanna see that painting.
我也不记得是谁告诉我的了
Can't remember who told me about it,
但我相信现在都无所谓了
but I'm pretty sure it doesn't matter much anymore.
不知道你有没有听说
Don't know if you heard what happened.
听说什么
W-what happened?
原来和你打交道的那些人
Well, those people you used to deal with.
我们全副武装的兄弟姐妹
Our brothers and sisters in arms and operation,
他们已经不再管事了
well, they've been removed from the field of play.
兄弟姐妹
Uh, brothers and sisters?
你...是什么意思
What -- W-w-what do you mean?
我觉得你知道是什么意思
I think you know what it means.
意思是我们得谈谈
It means we need to talk!
真是...
Just...
关于昨天晚上的事
In -- in regarding last night,
我明白你的意思了
m-m-message received.
很清楚
Loud and clear.
什么意思
What was the message?
你说你很清楚
You said it was loud and clear.
我觉得你是想让我们明白谁才是老大
Just I -- I think you were showing us who was boss, right?
靠
Yeah. Shit.
真是...
It's just...
美到窒息
It's just breathtaking.
是啊
Yeah.
他就是统治的榜样
See, that's management by example.
你总得处理这些事
Crap you got to deal with, right?
还用你说
You're telling me.
昨天晚上
So, last night,
是我们努力想办法
that was us working our asses off
让你看到了一个榜样
to provide you an example.
你这地方不错
You got a nice place.
高墙
Tall walls.
这里的人说不定都忘了
People in here probably forget
行尸的模样
what the corpses look like...
行尸的味道
...what they smell like.
我们本打算为你杀了它们
Now, we were gonna kill them for you,
来提醒你  我们能提供的服务
to remind you of the service we can provide,
但你们自己收拾了残局
and you cleaned up the mess yourselves.
真不错
Good on you.
我们肯定是从你们那里学了不少本事
Well, we must have picked up some skills from your people.
如果你好好想想
Uh, if you think about it...
还是你们救了我们  对吧
you still saved us, right?
这样想很不错
Well, that's a nice way to look at it.
我很欣赏
I appreciate that.
我有团队精神
Well, I'm a team player, you know?
我想这就是为什么大家选了我
I-I-I-I think that's why the people chose me.
你之前打交道的那些人
Well, the other people of ours your were dealing with? Yeah?
我想他们
I think they...
跟你这这样的人合作被惯坏了
got spoiled working with a guy like you.
-好吧  -确实
- Yeah, well... - Yeah.
-我觉得他们可能有些心慈手软了  -是啊
- I think they might've got a little soft. - Yeah.
所以才会被赶尽杀绝
It's what got them butchered, I imagine.
他们死了吗
They're dead?
死透了
Very, very dead.
相当透
Extremely dead.
但是  这事已经解决了
But, you know, it all worked out.
因为杀了他们的那些人
Because the people that killed them,
现在为我们卖命了
they work for us now.
要知道他们可是很能干
And they are real go-getters, you know?
真是遗憾
It's, um...a shame
会发生这种事
when things like that have to happen, you know?
拜托  告诉尼根
Please, tell Negan
我明白合作的好处
I understand the benefits in, uh...crossing the aisle.
不
No.
没必要了
No reason for that.
没必要了吗
No?
因为  现在
Because, for now,
我就是你的尼根
I'm your Negan.
因为尼根想这样
'Cause that's what Negan wants.
但还是谢谢你
But thank you.
你能明白我们带来的好处  这意义重大
It means a lot that you recognize what we bring to the table.
这也是你为什么还在这
That's why you're still here, and...
而其他人不在了
others aren't.
明白吗
Understand?
我明白
Oh, I understand.
很好
Good.
是啊
Yeah.
这样很好  很好
It is. It's good. It's good.
-还有什么想告诉我的吗  -没了
- Anything else you want me to know? - No.
还有什么幺蛾子需要我留意吗
Any hitches in the giddyap I should be aware of?
格雷戈里
Gregory?
确实还有
Actually, there is.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you serious?
-这是...  -威士忌
- This is, uh-- - ‭Scotch.
不是普通的...
Well, not just --
我不喜欢
Hate the stuff.
喝起来像烟灰缸和玻璃清洁剂
Tastes like, um, ashtrays and window cleaner.
我喜欢琴酒
I'm a gin man.
不过看起来确实是好货
But this does look like it could harden a connoisseur.
态度不错
What a gesture.
你说你不喜欢
You say you hate it?
尼根会喜欢的
Negan'll love this.
我会跟他说是我送的  不提你了
Now, I'm gonna say it's from me, not mention you, okay?
我真的很想抢这个功劳
I really want the headline on this one.
-好吗  -但是
- Okay? - ‭But, uh --
你不把那瓶放回去吗
You want to slide that one back in?
抱歉  不该用问句
Sorry. I shouldn't ask.
你给老子把那瓶放回去
You want to slide that one back in, period.
这可是大事  格雷戈里
This is big, Gregory.
天大的事
It's huge.
我不会忘的
And I won't forget it.
万分感谢
I really, really appreciate this.
谢谢你
Thank you.
现在我们要扫荡一遍
Now, we're gonna go through the place
拿走你所有东西的一半
and take half of everything you have.
但只拿一半
But only half.
把这放到尼根卡车上
Take this to the Negan truck, okay?
出去  先生们  干活了
Exeunt, gentlemen! Get to work.
还有  把画拿走
Oh, and take the painting.
最后一件事  格雷戈里
One last thing, Gregory.
你能给我跪下吗
Could I just get a kneel out of you?
你说什么
Excuse me?
跪下
Kneel.
跪得真实在  格雷戈里
That's a solid kneel, Gregory.
记得下次也要
You remember that for next time.
我觉得尼根不在这
I don't think Negan's here.
没看到他那辆黑卡车
I don't see that black truck.
你并不是出来兜风的
You weren't taking a drive.
也不是来找我的
You weren't coming to get me.
我不能就这么放过他们
I can't let them get away with this.
- 你知道我不能  - 我知道
- You know I can't. - I know.
和我一起去吧
Come with me.
你也想杀掉他们
You want to kill them, too.
我们可以做到的
We can do it.
你自己说过
You said it.
这是为了我们自己
It'd be for us.
不是为了亚伯拉罕  不是为了格伦
Not for Abraham, not for Glenn.
不是为了玛姬
Not for Maggie.
你是为自己做的
You're doing it for you.
是的
Yeah.
如果一切顺利
So if it all goes right...
你做到了
...and you do it...
-你要怎么逃掉  -不重要
- ...how do you get away? - It wouldn't matter.
对我很重要
It would to me.
求你别去
Please don't go.
和我走吧
Just come with me.
-你逃不掉的  -我会回家的
- You can't make it -- - I'm just gonna go home.
-你骗我  -不  我没有
- You're lying. - No, I'm not.
你不该去
You shouldn't go.
但我也不能阻止你
But I can't stop you.
他们会看到你的
They'll see you.
不会的
No. They won't.
我让你把她们藏在走廊的壁橱里
I told you to hide them in the hallway closet!
不  你只说了"壁橱"
No, you said "Closet."
这是我的卧室
This is my bedroom.
如果他们进来时我还没...
What if they came in here before I --
还没来得及把我们供出去吗
Before you tried to give us up?
他们会先杀掉你的
They would've killed you first.
-甜心  我在和耶稣说话  -够了
- Honey, I'm talking to Jesus. - Stop.
你为什么要维护她
Why are you even defending her?
我们变成现在这样就是因为她和瑞奇
We're here right now because she and -- and Rich
没能履行诺言
didn't handle things like they said they would.
救世军想要杀掉你
The Saviors tried to kill you.
那是个误会
That was a misunderstanding.
等救世军一离开
And as soon as the Saviors leave,
就把她们送走
we get them the hell out of here
-省得真的发生惨剧  -别说了
- before something bad really happens. - Stop!
她们要留下
They're staying.
或者你想公之于众
Or do you want to make it public?
让大家知道你和亚历山大做的交易吗
You want to make the deal with Alexandria public?
丢掉你装糊涂的机会
Lose your plausible deniability?
丢掉你的权位
Lose your position?
-这么说你现在要掌权了  -不是
- So you're gonna be in charge now? - No.
只不过不再是你说的算了
It's just that you won't be.
玛姬和萨沙会留在这
Maggie and Sasha are staying.
我也会留在这
I'm staying.
我们会成为一个不正常的欢乐大家庭
We're all gonna be one big happy dysfunctional family.
那就这样吧
So we will be.
我来保证我们的安全
And I'll see us through this.
我今天和他们达成了进展
I made progress with them today.
-你也看到了  -我看到的不是那样
- You saw it. - That's not what I saw.
是吗  反正就是这么回事
Yeah? Well, it's what happened.
我们好好配合  他们就会善待我们
We play nice, they play nice.
明白吗  亲爱的
See, dear?
救世军实际上是很讲道理的
Saviors can actually be quite reasonable.
这是块好表
It's a fine watch.
没必要丢在外面淋雨
Doesn't need to be left out in the rain.
这里现在也是我们的家了
This is our home now.
你要开始学会叫对我名字
So you'll learn to start to call me by my name.
不是玛莎  不是亲爱的  不是甜心
Not Marsha, not "Dear," Not "Honey."
玛姬
Maggie.
玛姬·李
Maggie Rhee.
我来的时候  格雷戈里已经掌权了
When I got here, Gregory was already in charge.
我当时以为大家出于某种原因选了他
Thought the people chose him for a reason.
现在想起来  可能只是凑巧而已
Looking at it now, I think it just happened.
我不喜欢他的做法
I didn't like how he did things.
但是我心中没有取代他的人选
But I couldn't imagine anyone else in his place.
现在我有了
I can now.
谁
Who?
我们以后再谈
We'll talk about it sometime.
我应该早点跟格雷戈里谈的
I should've talked to Gregory sooner.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但愿  你们能让我做出补偿
Hopefully, you'll let me make it up to you.
我们会的
We will.
门关了
The gates are closed.
等等  他们还在外面装货
Wait, they're still loading up outside.
拖车里见
I'll see you back at the trailer.
如果你想补偿我们
If you want to make it up to us...
你能找到尼根的住处吗
...can you find where Negan lives?
其中一辆卡车会回那里  所以...
One of the trucks is going back there,so...
是的  我可以找到
yeah, I can do that.
你能保密吗  只有我们俩知道
Can you keep it between us, just you and me?
不告诉玛姬吗
No Maggie?
我不喜欢这样
I don't like that.
我也不喜欢
Me neither.
你来了
You're here.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不好
I'm not.
但我会好的
But I will be.
人们说你开拖拉机杀了行尸
People told me you killed walkers and a car...
毁了车
with a tractor?
我当时不能袖手旁观
I couldn't sit by and watch.
我不会再那样了
Not again.
所以我坐着做了一些事
So I guess I sat and did something.
-你应该保重身体的  -那不难
- You're supposed to take it easy. - It wasn't hard.
不是我第一次了
It wasn't the first time.
高中时有个男生
There was this boy in high school.
你开车碾了他
You ran over the boy?
他的车
His car.
之前是辆大黄蜂
It was a Camaro.
后来不是了
And then it wasn't.
伊妮德
Enid.
我是来帮忙的
I -- I came to help.
你独自来的吗
You came by yourself?
是的
Yeah.
吃点晚饭吧
Have some dinner.
亚伯拉罕的墓上为什么有气球
Why are there balloons on Abraham's grave?
我不忍心告诉你
I didn't have the heart to tell you.
格伦会告诉你的
Glenn would've.
他最不会说谎了
He was a bad liar.
抱歉
Sorry.
不必道歉
There's no need to be sorry.
气球没什么不好
Nothing wrong with balloons.
坟墓上没有标记
There's nothing marking the graves.
不
Nope.
我本打算在格伦的墓上放这个
I was gonna use this for Glenn's.
是我爸爸的
It was my dad's.
他送给了他
He gave it to him.
但是我现在要送给你
But I'm giving it to you.
我们不需要任何东西来铭记他
We don't need anything to remember him by.
有我们就够了
We have us.
感谢上帝  为你每个早晨给我们第一道曙光
For this new morning, with its light,
为你在夜晚给我们安歇和住所
for rest and shelter of the night,
为你给我们健康和食物
for health and food,
为你给我们爱和朋友
for love and friends,
为你一切美好的恩赐
for everything that goodness sends.
阿门
Amen.
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - ‭Amen.